Silent. Invisible. Invincible. He’s in town with a few days to kill.
Predator 2 is a science fiction, action, thriller
film directed by Stephen Hopkins.
A police chief in the war-torn streets of Los Angeles discovers that an
extraterrestrial creature is hunting down residents - and that he is the next target.
Lieutenant Mike Harrigan, played by Danny Glover.
Peter Keyes, played by Gary Busey.
Danny Archuleta, played by Rubén Blades.
Leona Cantrell, played by María Conchita Alonso.
Jerry Lambert, played by Bill Paxton.
Captain Phil Heinemann, played by Robert Davi.
Predator 2 is a 1990 American science fiction horror film, written by brothers Jim and John Thomas, directed by Stephen
Hopkins, and starring Danny Glover, Gary Busey, Rubén Blades, María Conchita Alonso, Bill Paxton, and Robert Davi.
It is the second installment of the Predator franchise, with
Kevin Peter Hall reprising his role as the Predator.
Set ten years after the events of the first film, Predator 2 focuses on a disgruntled police detective
and his allies battling a malevolent and technologically advanced extraterrestrial.
Predator 2 was released on November 21, 1990, and grossed $57 million.
Although it initially received generally negative reviews,
the film has since gained a cult following.
It was followed by the crossover film Alien vs.
Predator in 2004, and a third mainline installment, Predators, in 2010.
The film explores themes of predator, war on drugs,
extraterrestrial technology, alien, los angeles, california.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.